Register of the Edgerton Public Schools Records, 1921-1976
Wisconsin Historical Society
Edgerton Public Schools Records, 1921-1976
Edgerton Public Schools (Wis.)
Rock Series 40
2.0 c.f. (5 archives boxes)
Housed at the University Archives Area Research Center, Harold Andersen Library, University of Wisconsin-Whitewater; owned by the Wisconsin Historical Society, Library-Archives Division
Minutes of the school board, 1921-1976; clerk's record, 1930-1942; and annual reports of the school district plus some rural school districts consolidated into the Edgerton system, 1922-1971. The clerk's record book contains primarily financial information with some correspondence. The annual reports usually list financial information, number of pupils, and name and number of teachers. Schools are located in Rock County unless otherwise noted.
Minutes are chronological. Annual reports are grouped by township, or if a joint district, are by district number after the others.
Contents List
- Minutes, 1921-1976
  - 1921-1947 (Box 1)
  - 1947-1958 (Box 2)
  - 1958-1969 (Box 3)
  - 1970-1976 (Box 4)
- Clerk's Record, 1930-1942 (Box 1)
- Annual Reports, 1922-1971
  - Albion, District No. 2, Albion State Graded School, 1959-1960 (Box 5)
  - Albion, District No. 6, Red Brick School, 1933-1953 (Box 5)
  - Edgerton, Common and High School, 1922-1952 (Box 5)
  - Fulton, District No. 2, Cox School, 1948-1961 (Box 2)
  - Fulton, District No. 4, Indian Ford School, 1927-1961 (Box 5)
  - Fulton, District No. 8, 1944, 1954 (Box 5)
  - Porter, District No. 3, Eagle School, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Porter, District No. 6, Lienau School, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Joint District No. 1, Towns of Porter, Center, and Dunkirk (Dane County), 1959-1961 (Box 5)
  - Joint District No. 1, Towns of Sumner (Jefferson County) and Albion (Dane County), Busseyville School, 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Joint District No. 2, Towns of Albion (Dane County) and Sumner (Jefferson County), Gravel Store School, 1947-1954 (Box 2)
  - Joint District No. 3, Towns of Fulton, Center, Porter, and Janesville, Fulton School, 1953-1956 (Box 5)
  - Joint District No. 7, Towns of Porter and Center, Stevens School, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Joint District No. 7, Towns of Fulton and Milton, Newville School, 1925-1960 (Box 2)
  - Joint District No. 8, Towns of Porter and Dunkirk (Dane County), 1958-1959 (Box 5)
  - Joint District No. 8, City of Edgerton and Towns of Fulton, Porter, Center, Janesville, and Milton (Rock County); Towns of Albion and Dunkirk (Dane County), and Town of Sumner (Jefferson County), Miscellaneous Reports, 1940-1952 and Annual Reports, 1953-1971 (Box 5)